Register of the Alfred M. Lilienthal papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- MIDDLE EAST PERSPECTIVE FILE, 1968-1986 (Boxes 106-125)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - Printers
        - Design Print, Inc. (Box-folder 112: 1)
        - Robertson Printers (Box-folder 112: 2)
        - Wickersham Print Co. (Box-folder 112: 3)
      - Publishers, for use of their book reviews (Box-folder 112: 4)
      - Readers (Box-folder 112: 5-6)
      - Receivers of sample issues (Box-folder 112: 7)
      - Subscribers
        - General
          - 1968-1969 (Box-folder 112: 8)
          - 1974-1976 (Box-folder 112: 9)
          - 1977-1981 (Box-folder 113: 1)
        - Key
          - 1967-1969 (Box-folder 113: 2)
          - 1968-1970 (Box-folder 113: 3)
          - 1971-1976 (Box-folder 113: 4)
        - Special (Box-folder 114: 1)
      - Translators (Box-folder 114: 2)
      - Writers (active or potential)
        - General (Box-folder 114: 3)
        - McMorris, Samuel Carter (Box-folder 114: 4)
    - Brownfeld, Allan (Box-folder 114: 5)
    - Expedite Service (Box-folder 114: 6)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box-folder 114: 7-8)
    - MEMSI (Middle East Management Services, Inc.) (Box-folder 114: 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 114: 10)
    - New York State Board of Social Welfare (Box-folder 114: 11)
    - Siddique, Kaubab (editor) (Box-folder 114: 12)
    - Strong, Marianne (publicity) (Box-folder 114: 13)
    - Taylor-Walker Associates (Box-folder 114: 14)
    - United States. Postmaster General (Box-folder 114: 15)
  - Financial statements. See also CORRESPONDENCE, Anaf Foundation (Box-folder 115: 1)
  - Form letters
    - General (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - (first appeal for subscriptions), 1968, May (Box-folder 115: 3)
    - 1970-1973 (Box-folder 115: 4)
    - 1972-1975 (Box-folder 115: 5)
    - 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 6)
    - - "What Kind of an Israel?" (written in February). Includes mailing lists, correspondence, and responses, 1983, April 4 (Box-folder 115: 7)
  - Founding documents (Box-folder 115: 8)
  - Inquiries (Box-folder 115: 9)
  - Issues
    - Printed copies, 1968-1986 (Box-folder 116: 1-8)
    - Drafts and research material
      - 1972-1982 (Box-folder 117: 1-8)
      - 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 1-7)
      - 1984-1985 (Box-folder 119: 1-4)
  - Mailing lists (Box-folder 119: 5)
  - Memoranda (Box-folder 119: 6)
  - Minutes of board of directors annual meetings. Includes list of board members (Box-folder 119: 7-9)
  - Political philosophy (Box-folder 120: 1)
  - Publicity material. Includes a description of Middle East Perspective by Charles W. Carruth (Box-folder 120: 2-5)
  - Subject file
    - Anne Frank diary - Controversy over Robert Edwards' article in the issue. See also CORRESPONDENCE, British Anti-Zionist Organization; Greenstein, Tony; Ghilan, Maxim, January 1981 (Box-folder 120: 6-8)
    - Dissolution. Includes interview of AML upon publication of last issue, 1985 (Box-folder 120: 9)
    - Incorporated status (Box-folder 120: 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 120: 11)
    - Myth-information (campaign exposing inaccuracies, bias, and misinformation in the media) (Box-folder 121: 1-6)
    - Organizational activities (Box-folder 121: 7)
    - Patxot, I. M. (Box-folder 121: 8)
    - Penetration of AML's office (Box-folder 121: 9)
    - Polls
      - 1971 (Box-folder 121: 10)
      - 1972 (Box-folder 121: 11)
    - Rent
      - General (Box-folder 121: 12)
      - Correspondence with Darryl Hickman (Box-folder 121: 13)
    - World Composition Services (Box-folder 121: 14)
  - Writings of AML
    - General, 1971-1982 (Box-folder 122: 1-12)
    - "Book and Perspective" column
      - 1972-1976 (Box-folder 123: 1)
      - 1973, December-1974, February (Box-folder 123: 2)
      - 1974
        - January-June (Box-folder 123: 3)
        - July-October (Box-folder 123: 4)
      - 1974, October-1975, January (Box-folder 123: 5)
      - 1975
        - January-April (Box-folder 123: 6)
        - April-August (Box-folder 124: 1)
        - August-September (Box-folder 124: 2)
        - October-December (Box-folder 124: 3)
      - 1976
        - January-December (Box-folder 124: 4)
        - January-May (Box-folder 124: 5)
        - June-August (Box-folder 124: 6)
        - September-December (Box-folder 125: 1)
      - 1977
        - January-June (Box-folder 125: 2)
        - June-September (Box-folder 125: 3)
        - October-December (Box-folder 125: 4)
      - 1977, December-1978, June (Box-folder 125: 5)
      - 1978, June-December (Box-folder 125: 6)
      - 1979, January-May (Box-folder 125: 7)
- PRINTED MATTER, 1953-1987 (Boxes 126-145)
  Journals, magazines, newsletters, and newspapers, arranged alphabetically; and clippings, arranged chronologically. In English and Arabic.
  - Journals, magazines, newsletters, and newspapers, arranged alphabetically
    - Arabic (Box 126)
    - English
      - A (Boxes 127-129)
      - A-H (Box 129)
      - I-J (Box 130)
      - J (Boxes 131-134)
      - J-N (Box 135)
      - N-P (Box 136)
      - P-T (Box 137)
      - V-Y (Box 138)
  - Clippings, arranged chronologically. Mainly in English
    - 1955-1964 (Box 139)
    - 1967-1974 (Box 140)
    - 1972-1982 (Box 141)
    - 1978-1982 (Box 142)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 143)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 144)
    - . Includes clippings on "Arabs, Israelis, and World Jewry," 1956-, 1983- (Box 145)
- CARD FILE, 1957-1978 (Box 146)
  Calling cards and index cards of readers' responses to Goes the Middle East(1957), The Other Side of the Coin (1965), and The Zionist Connection (1978).
  - Calling cards (Box 146)
  - Index cards of readers' responses to There Goes the Middle East (1957), The Other Side of the Coin (1965), and The Zionist Connection, (1978)
- OVERSIZE MATERIAL, 1936-1981 (Boxes 147-151)
  13 scrapbooks of clippings mentioning Lilienthal, press releases, and correspondence. In English and Arabic.
- MOTION PICTURE FILM, 1959
  - "The Turbulent Middle East," 2 reels (Film shelf)
    Access
    Use copy reference number: 82070_f_0003791
- TAPES, 1954-1991 (Box Vault)
  Sound tape reels, sound cassettes, and videocassettes of Lilienthal's speeches and interviews.
  General note
  * Cassette (C); reel-to-reel tape (R); video tape (V)
  - a) Sound recording of letter to Anthony Lewis ( New York Times), C (Item 1, Item (1))
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Use copy reference number: 82070_a_0000079
  - b) Dictation re sabotage of The Zionist Connection by Dodd Mead
  - a) Debate with Sidney Zion on TV program "Advise and Dissent" Part I, C (Item 2, Item (2))
  - b) Part II
  - a&b) Speech at UC Berkeley, CA, 2/15/83; C (Item 3, Item (2))
  - a) Sound recording of Spiro Agnew on Zionism, 5/76; C (Item 4, Item (3))
    Use copy reference number: 82070_a_0000078_a
  - a&b) Spiro Agnew on "Kup's show," Ch.31, UHF, 6/6/76; C (Item 5, Item (3))
  - a) Phone conversation re Camp David on "As It Happens," CBC Radio Network, C (Item 6, Item (5))
  - a&b) Appearance on Barry Farber's show, WMCA, 1971; C (Item 8, Item (6))
  - a) CJAD Montreal, 5/13/81; C (Item 7, Item (5))
  - a) Talk on Deir Yassin Day at American University of Beirut (AUB), Lebanon, 4/15/73; C (Item 9, Item (7I))
  - b) Question and answer period
  - a&b) Speech, Ohio University, Athens, OH, 2/12/81; C (Item 10, Item (8))
  - a) Braden-Buchanan show, WRC Radio, 3/13/80; C (Item 11, Item (10))
  - a) Reply to CBS editorial, 5/4/79; C (Item 12, Item (11))
  - a) Interview by press syndicate, Midweek #608, WTJX TV, St. Thomas, Virgin Islands, 1/4/79; C (Item 13, Item (14))
  - b) Hamilton Fish re Israel on John Collins' "Night Line," WVWI -CBS affiliate, 1/29/79
  - a) John Cooley - Trip I, C (Item 14, Item (17))
  - a) Answer to CBS editorial (Sue Cott), 11/75; C (Item 15, Item (18))
  - b) Debate with Martin Abend re Zionism, Metromedia, 11/75
  - a) Crossfire - Rochester, 1969; C (Box 159, Tape 16, Item 16, Item (19))
  - a) Moshe Dayan on "Meet the Press,", 2/12/78; C (Item 17, Item (22))
  - a&b) Coast-to-coast broadcast to 17 cities of speech "Where Goes the Middle East?" from Islamic Center in Detroit, MI, 3/1/70; C (Item 18, Item (23))
  - a) Same as Tape 18, but better recording (except short of 5 minutes), C (Item 19, Item (24))
  - b) Khankhan interviews; Mrs. Sirhan
  - a) Former Israeli ambassador Simcha Dimitz on BBC, London, UK, Led to equal time demand appearance of AML on "The World Tonight": "Israel and World Opinion," 10/30/80, 10/29/80.; C (Item 20, Item (25))
  - a) Sound recording of telephone conversation with Salsbury ( New York Times), who refused to publish AML's article re Einstein and Israel, C (Item 21, Item (26))
    Use copy reference number: 82070_a_0000082
  - b) Calif and Mohamed Mehdi letter - Kowity on Mohamed Mehdi
  - a&b) Barry Farber, WMCA AM, New York City, 6/4/79; C (Box 159, Item 22, Item (30))
  - a) Frustration re media; ad in New York Times (double standard), C (Item 23, Item (33))
  - b) Ad, 9/14
  - a) Ted Furey ( New York Times): controversy over ad, 3/17; C (Item 24, Item (34))
  - b) Executor Nathan re Einstein's attitude toward Israel
  - a) Phone interview from room in Hotel Nova Scotia with CBC Radio for "Information Morning Program" of Don Donelly and Don Tremain, Halifax, Canada, 11/13/79; C (Item 25, Item (36))
  - a) Promotion of The Zionist Connection on Don Harron's "Morning Side," CBC, Toronto, Ontario, 3/9/79; C (Item 26, Item (37))
  - a) Speech, American Humanist Association, New York City, 11/14/77; C (Item 27, Item (39))
  - a) I. L. Kennen, editor of Middle East Report, Washington, D.C., answer to 3/10/74, 3/17/74:; C (Item 28, Item (40))
  - a) Jack Jayes defends Dodd Mead, 5/8/78; C (Item 29, Item (28))
  - a) Defense of Larry King (who cancelled AML's appearance on his show) by Joan S. of Dodd Mead, 1/18/79; C (Item 30, Item (41))
  - b) Dictation re Tannenbaum and Soviet Jewry
  - a&b) News 8, "Probe," ABC TV, Dallas, TX, 4/2/79; C (Item 31, Item (43), Box 159)
  - a) Speech on Zionism and Racism, Tripoli, Libya, 7/25/76; C (Item 32, Item (44))
  - b) End of speech; Gotfried Newburger, 7/25/76
  - a&b) Speech at Consumnes River College, Sacramento, CA, 5/4/76; C (Item 33, Item (45))
  - a&b) Larry King Show on The Zionist Connection, Mutual Network, 4/15/79; C (Item 34, Item (46))
  - Continuation of Tape 34, C (Item 35, Item (46))
  - Continuation of Tape 35, C (Item 36, Item (46))
  - a) George Ball [from 209 to 256 only], C (Item 37, Item (51))
  - a) Sound recording of Menuhin (tape #5), C (Item 38, Item (52))
    Use copy reference number: 82070_a_0000081
  - a) Joseph Harsch; Ashraf Ghorbal; Quandt; Platt; Harold Michaels ( Christian Science Monitor), C (Item 39, Item (53))
  - b) Harold Michaels: controversy re the Christian Science Monitor's review and discussion of the CIA
  - a) Harold Michaels re the Christian Science Monitor, C (Item 40, Item (54))
  - a&b) Debate with Sol Stern on "Midday," Ch.5., New York, 10/8/80; C (Item 41, Item (55))
  - a) Middle East diary and interviews of Nuri Pasha, Jamali, King Hussein, Mahmoud Younes, R (Item 42, Item (56))
  - b) Hassan Heikal, Samir Rifai, and Prince Mashur of Saudi Arabia singing
  - a&b) Appearance on Mark Miller's show "In Depth," KCBS, San Francisco, CA, (aired 5/15 on the 28th anniversary of Israel). See also Tape 136, 5/6/76; C (Item 43, Item (57))
  - a) TV Guide; Moise; Time; Journal; argument over ad and with William F. Buckley, Jr. at time of UN Resolution equating Zionism with Racism, 11/75; C (Item 44, Item (58))
  - b) Debate with Martin Abend re Zionism, Ch.5, New York City, ?/75, 8/15
  - a) Nantucket interviews I, Summer 1971; C (Item 45, Item (59))
  - a) Conversation at Nantucket with Mrs. Rand and Marta Davies re Zionism, Summer 1971; C (Item 46, Item (61))
  - a) Interview by Nobile, (or 78), 11/22/79; C (Item 47, Item (62))
  - b) Nantucket
  - a) Nantucket, Summer 1971; C (Item 48, Item (62))
  - b) Conversation with Bud Gifford, president of Providence Bank and director of Nantucket Bank re Berger and Hellers, Nantucket, Summer 1971
  - a&b) Speech and question and answer period, New York State University, New Paltz, NY, 5/1/79; C (Item 49, Item (63))
  - a) Speech, Phoenix Club, AZ, 3/25/79; C (Item 50, Item (65))
  - a) Conversation with Pomerantz re AML's letter to the New York Times, c., 10/30/77; C (Item 51, Item (66))
  - a) Conversation with Butler, public affairs VP of Mutual Broadcasting, re cancellation of AML's appearance on the Larry King Show, 1979; C (Item 52, Item (67))
  - a) Press conference, Montreal, Canada, 3/5/79; C (Item 53, Item (68))
  - b) The Zionist Connection: recitation of monstrous activities of Dodd, Mead
  - a) Interview for radio workshop, Sacramento, CA, 5/4/76; C (Item 54, Item (71))
  - a) Kay Radke of Dodd Mead and Joan S. the next day, 4/9/79; C (Item 55, Item (72))
  - b) Phone conversation with Siegel ( New York Times) about AML's letter to the editor
  - a) Kay Radke: pressures from Dodd Mead, which refuses to pay promotion expenses for AML's book, 2/9-10/79; C (Item 56, Item (73))
  - b) Kay Radke; Jack Jayes; Peter Taylor, 2/15-16/79
  - a) Speech, Sacramento College, CA, aired on AM and FM radio on, 5/13/76; C (Item 57, Item (74))
  - a&b) Speech, Mormon Assembly Hall, Salt Lake City, Utah, 10/15/70; C (Item 58, Item (75))
  - a&b) Speech, Holiday Inn, San Francisco, CA, 3/16/79; C (Item 59, Item (76))
  - a&b) Speech and question and answer period, UC Santa Barbara, CA, 4/23/76; C (Item 60, Item (77))
  - Short spots, CBS: Kotch, Hellstrom Chronicle, R (Item 61, Item (78))
  - Continuation of Tape 61, R (Item 62, Item (78))
  - a) Kathy Telch ( New York Times), 1/24; C (Item 63, Item (79))
  - b) Halo Lahe... (?)
  - a) Harding Bancroft ( New York Times), c. 1973; C (Item 64, Item (80))
  - a&b) Debate with Morris Levinson, national vice chairman of ZOA, University of Texas at El Paso, TX, 11/26/69; C (Item 65, Item (81))
  - a&b) Speech, 18th Annual Unitarian Universalist General Assembly, Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, (with an introduction by John N. Booth), 6/27/79; C (Item 66, Item (82))
  - a&b) Speech, "Where Goes the Middle East?" Library Associates, University Club, Washington, D.C., (after Ronald Reagan's election), 11/19/80; C (Item 67, Item (83I))
  - a) End of question and answer period, C (Item 68, Item (83II))
  - a&b) Debate with Bob Grant, WMCA Radio Metromedia, New York City, 11/13/74; C (Item 69, Item (85))
  - b) Debate with Martin Abend, 11 and/or 12/74
  - a) UJA program, WOR, 10/26/75; C (Item 70, Item (86))
  - a) Press conference, Brigham Young University, Provo, UT,; and debate with S. G. Rich of the University of Utah, Provo, 10/25/73, C (Item 71, Item (87))
  - a) Debate with Martin Abend, Metromedia TV, Ch.5, New York City, re the Sinai, 9/5/75, and re Zionism, 8/15/75; C (Item 72, Item (88))
  - a) Debate with David Schoenbrum re the PLO on WPIX TV, New York City,; and with Martin Abend, Metromedia TV, Ch.5, New York City, 11/14/74, 10/29/74; C (Item 73, Item (89))
  - a) General Brown at Duke University Law School,; debate with Martin Abend, Ch.5, and with Elmer Berger, Ch. 11, 11/14/74; C (Item 74, Item (90))
  - b) Bob Grant's phone retraction, 11/19/74
  - a&b) AML in Bahrain: questions and answers re Arab public relations and education, C (Item 75, Item (93))
  - a) Reply to CBS editorial on UN Resolution equating Zionism with Racism, repeated 5 times (distributed as UN document A/10363 of November 17), 11/12-13/75; C (Item 76, Item (95))
  - b) Bachwan
  - a) CBS editorials, TV - Radio, 11/14/75; C (Item 77, Item (96))
  - a) Speech, "Where Goes the Middle East?" Columbia University, International Law Society, NY, 3/12/72; C (Item 78, Item (97))
  - a&b) Speech on "Palestine Day," Damascus, Syria, (substituted for Yasir Arafat), 5/15/75; C (Item 79, Item (98))
  - a) Speech, Information and Foreign Affairs Committees of the People's Assembly, Cairo, Egypt, 6/10/75; C (Item 80, Item (99))
  - b) Departure from Cairo; arrival in Libya; comments in New York City
  - a) Martin Abend's comments, 12/16+17+21+27/76; Clark Clifford on CBS TV, 12/27/76; Jimmy Carter re Palestine, C (Item 81, Item (101))
  - b) McNeil-Lehrer Report: "Mideast" year end, 12/29/76
  - a) Debate with Martin Abend re oil, the Middle East, and other topics, 12/5-6/76; C (Item 82, Item (102A))
  - a) Debate with Martin Abend, Metromedia TV, 2/19/74; C (Item 83, Item (102B))
  - a) Debate with Martin Abend, Metromedia TV, 6/8/74; C (Item 84, Item (102C))
  - a) Debate with Martin Abend, Ch., 5, 3/20/78; C (Item 85, Item (102D))
  - a) TV capsules: Martin Abend re the Middle East, 12/22-25/76; C (Item 86, Item (102E))
  - b) Tom Snyder: "Neo-Nazis," NBC TV, 11/22/76
  - a&b) Debate with Martin Abend, Women's National Republican Club, New York City, 12/2/80; C (Item 87, Item (102F))
  - a&b) Dave Marash: "Middle East Journal," CBS TV, (interviews of Rashid Hussein and others), 2/9-20/76; C (Item 88, Item (103))
  - a) I. F. Stone re Arabs on McNeil-Lehrer Report, 11/14/75; C (Item 89, Item (104))
  - a) Agronsky and Company re Anwar Sadat, NET TV, 12/23/76; C (Item 90, Item (105))
  - b) Agronsky and Company re Yitzhak Rabin, NET TV, 1/7/77
  - a) Martin Abend re Egypt, 1/77; Walter Cronkite re the Middle East, C (Item 91, Item (106))
  - a) Anwar Sadat's press conference, Blair House, Washington, D.C., 4/6/77; C (Item 92, Item (107))
  - b) Speech, "Zionist Manipulations to Induce Immigration to Israel," Libya, 1975
  - a) AML, Horowitz, and Van Zile on "Accent On" re the Arab Boycott, 5/12/77; C (Item 93, Item (108))
  - a) Arab Boycott program, Part II, (without AML); debate with Mohamed Mehdi on "Accent On", 11/14/77; C (Item 94, Item (109))
  - b) Felicia Langer, WBAI, 10/76
  - a) News debate with Bob Grant, WPIX TV, Ch.5, New York City,; debate with Martin Abend, Metromedia, Ch.5, Nw York City, 11/11/74, 11/8/74; C (Item 95, Item (110))
  - b) Yasir Arafat on "Issues and Answers,", 11/9/74
  - a) Debate with Bob Grant re the PLO, WMCA Radio, New York City,; Yasir Arafat and General Brown on CBS TV, 11/13/74; C (Item 96, Item (111))
  - b) Yasir Arafat on World Council of Churches panel, Metromedia TV, Ch., 5, 11/13/74
  - a) Debate with Bob Grant, WPIX TV, New York City, 10/16/74; C (Item 97, Item (112))
  - a) Bob Grant's apology to AML, WMCA Radio, 11/18/74; Isaacs on Jews in American Politics, C (Item 98, Item (113))
  - b) Yasir Arafat on "Perspective," ABC Radio, 11/17/74
  - a) Debate with Bob Grant, WPIX TV, 1/1/75; C (Item 99, Item (114))
  - a&b) Debate with Arnold Forster, former president of the ADL, on Barry Gray's show, WMCA, New York City, 11/1/74; C (Item 100, Item (115))
  - a&b) Headliner, Sunday Morning, WMAL TV, Washington, D.C., 3/10/74; C (Item 101, Item (116))
  - a) Holliday (of Brown), Monday after Easter; John Lythe, ABC; problems re ad; letter to Fulbr., C (Item 102, Item (117))
  - b), 4/3
  - a) Struggle over costs; Holliday, C (Item 103, Item (118))
  - b) Summary of, 4/17
  - a) CBS TV special "Death of a King" on King Faisal's assassination, 3/25/75; C (Item 104, Item (121))
  - a&b) King Faisal's assassination, 3/25/75: debate with Bob Grant, WPIX, New York City; debate with Martin Abend, Metromedia, Ch.5., New York City; AML's comments, WPIX; CBS/NBC/ABC TV news; Martin Abend and Mohamed Mehdi re King Faisal, C (Item 105, Item (122))
  - a) Interview of Abu Nidal, Hotel Vendome, Beirut, (just before Ma'alot - also used on BBC and ITV in London), 5/74; C (Item 106, Item (123))
  - b) Departure for the Middle East,; first visit to Qatar, 4/74
  - a) AML with Ted Furey and Steve Flanders on "Let's Find Out," WCBS, New York City, 11/10/74; C (Item 107, Item (124))
  - a) Ted Cavenau: blackmail re Martin Abend column, C (Item 108, Item (125))
  - b) Elmer Berger rebuts Cavenau
  - a) Robert Paradise ( Wall Street Journal); Bob Grant; Petroleum Week, C (Item 109, Item (127))
  - b) Crisis over ad; Robert Paradise; R. Henry; Jack Jayes; Kircher
  - a) Debate with Martin Abend, Metromedia, WPIX TV, 2/5/75; C (Item 110, Item (128))
  - a) Martin Abend, c., 75/76; C (Item 111, Item (129))
  - b) Conversation with Nobile; talk-show with Tobin (of Continental Oil)
  - a) Chester Pozey: fears of running ad in Wall Street Journal, C (Item 112, Item (130))
  - b) Wall Street Journal; Ted Phillips re USJ; Village Voice
  - a) Conversation with Harris Schnawi, WINS, Ch.11, re answer to Rabbi Tannenbaum, used four times c., 12/20/74; C (Item 113, Item (132))
  - b) Conversation with Pat Tobias
  - a) News debate re with David Schoenbrun, WPIX TV, New York City, 10/29/74; C (Item 114, Item (133))
  - a) Mrs. Sirhan, 9/70; C (Item 115, Item (135))
  - a) Promises by Tobin to hold a roundtable, C (Item 116, Item (136))
  - b) Visit to Tarrytown library: comments on book
  - a) Ted Furey's editorial on WCBS, and AML's answer, 12/2/74, 11/26-27/74; C (Item 117, Item (137))
  - a) Phone conversation with Don Walker, C (Item 118, Item (138))
  - a) Wall Street Journal: no help from Bill Rogers, Sue Reid, C (Item 119, Item (139))
  - b) Wall Street Journal refuses to run ad; Higgins; Wayne, 2/5-6
  - a) "Ford and the Boycott," WPIX TV, New York City,; and various AML commentaries centering on Saudi Arabia, 2/27/75; C (Item 120, Item (140))
  - a) Claudia Wright's comments in Riyadh re pressures on Australia, C (Item 121, Item (141))
  - a) Speech, Ohio University, Athens, 2/12/81; C (Item 122, Item (142))
  - b) End of speech; question and answer period
  - a) The Zionist Connection discussed with Moshe Kagan and Sheldon Ranz, WBAI (Producer, Valerie Van Isler), 10/22/81; C (Item 123, Item (143))
  - a) Dictation, 12/9/77 and 1978; C (Item 124, Item (144))
  - b), 9/17
  - a) Baghdad, Iraq, V: interview of Saad Hamadi; conversation at Beach Club in Kuwait with editor Chehouri of Al Qabas, 5/29/80; C (Item 125, Item (145))
  - b) Kuwait; VIP Lounge in Bahrain (AML predicts the assassination of Anwar Sadat [at 275]), (5/29-6/27)
  - a) Speech, "There Goes the Middle East," Oregon State University, Corvallis, OR, 2/18/83; C (Item 126, Item (146))
  - a) Talks with Gabby Baromky, acting president of Bir Zeit University; the former Governor of Jerusalem, in his law office; and refugees at a camp, 5/15-18/80; C (Item 127, Item (147))
  - a) Interview on student radio station, Carleton University, Ottawa, C (Item 128, Item (148))
  - a) Phone interview, WKPA, New Kensington, Pittsburgh, PA, Fall 1981; C (Item 129, Item (149))
  - a) Interview with call-in questions on Bob Grant's show, WMCA, New York City, 10/6/81; C (Item 130, Item (151))
  - a) Speech, College of Marin, Kentfield, CA, 5/6/76; C (Item 131, Item (201))
  - b) End of speech; question and answer period
  - a) End of question and answer period of Tape 131 (disruption by Jews for Jesus), C (Item 132, Item (202))
  - a) Speech, Orange Coast College, Costa Mesa, CA, 5/1/76; C (Item 133, Item (203))
  - b) End of speech; question and answer period
  - Same as Tape 133, C (Item 134, Item (204))
  - a) Speech and question and answer period, San Francisco State University, CA, 5/6/76; C (Item 135, Item (205))
  - b) End of question and answer period
  - a) "Sunday's Best," KCBS, San Francisco, CA, See also Tape 43, 5/15/76.; C (Item 136, Item (206))
  - a&b) Speech, Army Navy Club dinner, Washington, D.C., 5/1/75; C (Item 137, Item (207))
  - a) Reply to WCBS editorial of, 1/13-14/77, 1/18-19/77; C (Item 138, Item (252))
  - a) AML in Amman, Jordan: voices of Palestinian refugees, 3/29/69; C (Item 139, Item (253))
  - a) Discussion with Mohamed Mehdi on "Accent On" program entitled "An American Perspective on the Arab Boycott," WABC TV, 1/16/77; C (Item 140, Item (301))
  - b) Martin Abend; Kennan, 1/77
  - a) Appearance on "The World Tonight," BBC, London, UK: "Israel and World Opinion,", 10/30/80; C (Item 141, Item (600))
  - Same as Tape 141, C (Item 142, Item (600))